[{"question":" How can you minimise all views except for the currently selected view in the Eclipse interface?","options":[{"text":"Press Control-M (Windows) or Command-M (Mac)","correct":false},{"text":"Double-click the tab you want to maximise","correct":false},{"text":"all of these answers","correct":true},{"text":"Click the Maximise button at the top right of the view","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What happens when you execute the Run -> Skip all Breakpoints command?","options":[{"text":"All breakpoints are deleted","correct":false},{"text":"none of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"All breakpoints will not be fired when debugging and will not cause application execution to suspend","correct":true},{"text":"All breakpoints and bookmarks are disabled","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is not a key part of Eclipse projects and technologies?","options":[{"text":"Plug-in Development Environment (PDE)","correct":false},{"text":"Eclipse Project","correct":false},{"text":"Java Development Toold (JDT)","correct":true},{"text":"Eclipse .NET","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which is a valid way to create a code snippet?","options":[{"text":"Right-click the selected code and select Add to Snippets","correct":true},{"text":"Drag the code into the snippets view","correct":false},{"text":"Click Source -> Snippets -> Create Snippet","correct":false},{"text":"With the code selected, click the + button in the Snippets view","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" In this image, what does the circled button do?","options":[{"text":"It expands the comparison between the two files to include whitespace.","correct":false},{"text":"It allows you to delete the line of code to which it is connected.","correct":false},{"text":"It allows changes from one version of a file to be applied to another version of the file.","correct":true},{"text":"It allows you to merge both lines of code together.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When inserting a snippet containing variables into a source file, how are values for the variable defined?","options":[{"text":"Eclipse fills them in with a drop-down menu of available optons.","correct":false},{"text":"They are automatically highlighted in code.","correct":true},{"text":"They are populated using environment variables.","correct":false},{"text":"You populate them through a pop-up windows.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" How can you create a new Git branch in Eclipse?","options":[{"text":"all of these answers","correct":true},{"text":"Right-click your project in the Package Explorer and select Team -> Switch To -> New Branch","correct":false},{"text":"Click File -> New -> Git -> Branch","correct":false},{"text":"Click Source -> Team -> Switch To -> New Branch","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Why might you use the Open Type button?","options":[{"text":"to open a file by its name","correct":false},{"text":"to search the workbench for a class to open in an editor","correct":false},{"text":"to find a string in a text file","correct":false},{"text":"to find all places where a certain type is instantiated","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" In the JUnit view, what is the value in the parentheses after a previously run unit test?","options":[{"text":"the number of errors found in the test","correct":false},{"text":"the time it took the test to run","correct":true},{"text":"the name of the package containing the test class","correct":false},{"text":"the test class name","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". In this image, what does the circled icon in the Problems view do?","options":[{"text":"It sends the currently selected problem to another view.","correct":false},{"text":"It indents the currently selected problem.","correct":false},{"text":"It opens the Filter menu so you can customise what problems are displayed.","correct":true},{"text":"It jumps to the currently selected problem in the Editor.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What can you not do in the Expressions view?","options":[{"text":"track the value of a variable throughout the lifetime of the app.","correct":true},{"text":"change the name of a variable while debugging.","correct":false},{"text":"change the value of a final variable while debugging.","correct":false},{"text":"track values of variables when they are out of scope.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Your code is highlighted in red when running code coverage. Why is this?","options":[{"text":"The code is the cause of a compiler warning.","correct":false},{"text":"The method is unused or causes runtime errors.","correct":false},{"text":"The code is within an if statement that is always evaluated as true at runtime.","correct":false},{"text":"No code calls the method.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When selecting the Synchronise Workspace option for a project, what perspective is opened?","options":[{"text":"Git","correct":false},{"text":"Java","correct":false},{"text":"Team Synchronising","correct":true},{"text":"Remote Synchronise","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which is not a way to check the value of a variable while debugging?","options":[{"text":"Hover ove the variable in the Editor.","correct":false},{"text":"Check the Debug view.","correct":false},{"text":"Check the Variables view.","correct":false},{"text":"Watch the variable in the Expressions view.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you configure Eclipse to open a webpage in a browser outside of Eclipse using the Windows (Eclipse) -> Preferences -> General -> Web Browser dialog page?","options":[{"text":"Select Use external web browser.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Add a new browser and select the desired browser in the External web browsers menu.","correct":false},{"text":"Select Use external web browser, click the New or Search button, add your browser, and then select it in the External web browsers menu.","correct":true},{"text":"Use the Search button to search for an installed web browser.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What view, within the Team component, displays the commits related to a particular project or file?","options":[{"text":"Git Staging","correct":false},{"text":"History","correct":false},{"text":"Synchronize","correct":false},{"text":"Git Repositories","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is included in your wqorkspace folder?","options":[{"text":"a hidden .metadata folder","correct":false},{"text":"a hidden .metadata folder and projects imported into the workspace only","correct":false},{"text":"only projects imported into the workspace","correct":false},{"text":"a hidden .metadata folder and projects created in the workspace","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What can you not do in the Variables view?","options":[{"text":"monitor variables that are outside the scope of the current stack frame","correct":false},{"text":"set a breakpoint to track a particular instance","correct":false},{"text":"inspect the values of an object's fields","correct":false},{"text":"edit the value of a variable while the debugger is running your app","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is not a method stub that Eclipse will create for you in the New JUnit Test Case window?","options":[{"text":"tearDown()","correct":false},{"text":"setUpClass()","correct":false},{"text":"tearDownAfterClass()","correct":false},{"text":"setUp()","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does the Problems view show?","options":[{"text":"all of the answers","correct":false},{"text":"warnings and errors","correct":false},{"text":"code that does not match your formatting settings","correct":false},{"text":"threads containing errors","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When switching workspaces, what is preserved?","options":[{"text":"all preferences","correct":false},{"text":"none of these answers","correct":false},{"text":"the current perspective","correct":false},{"text":"preferences for a language (e.g., Java)","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you set files to save automatically when launching an application?","options":[{"text":"Click Window (Eclipse) -> Preferences -> Run/Debug -> Launching, and then select Save required dirty editors before launching.","correct":false},{"text":"Click Window (Eclipse) -> Preferences -> Java -> Editor -> Save Actions","correct":false},{"text":"Click File -> Save All.","correct":false},{"text":"Change the project's run configuration.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""}]